本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
谁想吃斯坦饼
Who wants Stan-cakes?
它们看起来很像煎饼
They're like pancakes,
但是里面大概有一些我的头发
but they probably have some of my hair in 'em.
不吃
Pass.
终于到了
It's here!
耶  终于到了  终于到了  终于到了  终于到了
Oh, it's here! It's here! It's here! It's here!
我等了一早上  它终于到了
I've been waiting all morning and it's finally here!
《重力泉八卦报》接收了我那篇
The Gravity Falls Gossiper accepted my article
关于松鼠夏天时尚建议的稿件
about summer fashion tips for squirrels.
我的照片终于要上报纸了
My picture is gonna be in the newspaper!
快看
Check it!
社会版 今夏最大盛事
帕西菲卡・诺斯韦斯特宣布
"Pacifica Northwest declares
V领是本季度的潮流
V-necks the look of the season."
我看的这是什么啊
What am I looking at here?
什  什么
Wha-wha-what?
看起来好像有人花重金上了头版
Looks like someone bought their way to the front page.
小孩子化妆成这样合法吗
Is it legal for a child to wear that much make-up?
帕西菲卡
Ugh. Pacifica.
她总是毁掉一切
She always ruins everything.
振作一点  梅宝
Aww, cheer up, Mabel.
我是说  现在已经没人读报了
I mean, no one even reads newspapers anymore.
伙计们
Dudes!
V领季就要来临了
V-neck season is upon us!
谁想帮我裁剪引领时尚
Who wants to help me get ahead of the fashion curve?
我要更进一步  裁出W领
I'm taking it one step further with the W-neck!
必须  紧跟  报纸
Must. Follow. Newspaper.
我需要一些东西来转移自己的注意力
I need something to get my mind off this.
想要从你不幸的生活当中
Looking for a distraction
寻找分散你注意力的东西吗
from your horrible life?
嘿  想啊
Why, yes!
胜利  荣誉
Victory. Honor.
命运  羊肉
Destiny. Mutton.
这些听上去过时的词  仍然在
These old timey sounding words are alive and well
重力泉皇家折扣高尔夫球场中闪耀
at the Gravity Falls Royal Discount Putt Hutt!
免责声明：小吃部不出售羊肉
对了  梅宝  你不是喜欢迷你高尔夫吗
Hey, Mabel, you love mini-golf!
她从小就一直打得很棒
She's been amazing at it since we were kids.
你说呢  梅宝
What do you say, Mabel?
这些天我们太紧张了
We've had a stressful couple of days.
不如放松一下吧
How about we take a break, huh?
在迷你高尔夫中胜过我们会让你开心点吗
Would kicking all our butts at mini-golf cheer you up?
也许会有一点
Maybe a little.
快来吧  梅宝  胜利
Come on, Mabel! Victory!
荣誉
Honor!
命运
Destiny!
羊肉
Mutton!
胜利  荣誉  命运  羊肉
Victory! Honor! Destiny! Mutton!
小猪会看好房子的
And the pig can look after the house.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： WaitinZ
翻译： moonywen  莫莉什么的  阿拱
■
校订  后期： Enpistu  WaitinZ
怪诞小镇  第二季第三集
Gravity Falls  S02E03  The Golf War
啊  迷你高尔夫  迷你冠军的运动
Ah, Mini-Golf. The sport of mini-champions.
草坪是假的  但快乐是真的
The grass is fake but the fun is real.
每个人都能从这里得到点什么
There's something here for everyone.
你  停下来
Hey, you, stop!
窝囊废
回来
Come back here!
嘿  那些手势很下流
Hey, those are lewd hand gestures!
注意力集中  集中  然后
Focus, focus, and...
别介意  老弟  你还是
Don't worry, bro, you're still
"嚎"厉害的
"Ext-roar-dinary!"
我就知足常乐吧
I'll take what I can get.
扭扭屁股这就开始
To the hip we go, and...
搞什么  我怎么会在这儿
Wha-- How'd I get here?
就是这样
Yes!
我的娘
Holy smokes!
我们家族中终于出了个人才
Someone in our family actually has talent.
斯坦叔公  好戏还在后头呢
Grunkle Stan, you ain't seen nothin' yet!
她是如此优秀
She's so good, yeah
看她怎样击球
Lookin' to hit that ball
看她非凡技巧
She's got the skills
将球直击进洞
Takin' it to the hole
伙计们  真是太厉害了
Guys, this is amazing.
如果梅宝再次一杆进洞
If Mabel gets a hole-in-one here,
她会打破她个人的最高纪录
she'll beat her all time high score!
你可以的  梅宝
You can do it, Mabel.
把那颗球当成帕西菲卡的脸
Pretend the ball is Pacifica's face.
真可恶
Aw, nuts!
不要太在意  孩子  世事无常
Ah, don't worry about it, kid. The thing's random.
没错  除了百慕大三角
Yeah, besides the Bermuda's Triangle,
迷你高尔夫也是世界上最神秘的事物
how mini golf works is the world's greatest mystery.
就我所知
As far as I'm concerned,
你仍然比重力泉里的其他人都要优
you're still better than anyone else is Gravity--
看看那边是谁啊
Oh, would you look at that?
我不知道今天原来是流浪汉高尔夫免费日啊
I didn't know it was "Hobos golf free" Day.
帕西菲卡
Pacifica!
这不是派恩斯家族吗
Well, if it isn't the Pines family.
胖子  老头  无聊  牙套
Fat, old, lame, braces.
苏斯  打小孩子有错吗
Soos, would it be wrong to punch a child?
让我来
I've got this.
帕西菲卡
Hey, Pacifica.
你们全家都是骗子那件事
How's that whole your-family-being-frauds thing
你感想如何啊
working out for you?
实际上  很好啊
Great, actually.
不过是些钱的问题
That's the thing about money.
它能让烦恼走开
It makes problems go away.
但是  有钱买不到技术
Well, can't buy you skill.
你面前的可是迷你高尔夫赛的冠军
You walked into the game of the mini golf champion.
谢尔盖
Sergei!
这是谢尔盖  我的教练
This is Sergei, my trainer.
迷你高尔夫曾上过一次体林匹克运动会
The Sportlympics had mini golf once.
冠军就是我
I took gold!
那么如果你不介意
So if you don't mind
把场地让给职业选手的话
moving out of the way of the professionals...
享受你的第二名吧  大家快给她鼓掌啊
Enjoy second place. Give her a hand, folks!
是吗
Oh, yeah?
好吧  我要重赛
Well, I want a rematch,
你  你
You-- you--
你这个只会漂白头发的肤浅富家拜金女
walking one dimensional bleached blonde valley girl stereotype!
那这样  来就来
Like, let's do this.
都听着  都听着
Hear ye! Hear ye!
立马打住
Stop at once!
因为天气原因公园要关门
The park is now closed due to weather.
迷你高尔夫之王有旨
The King of Mini Golf has spoken.
国王倒下了
Oh, the King is down!
这事没完  你  我  午夜
This isn't over. You. Me. Midnight.
咱们看看谁是最棒的
We'll see who's best.
我会来的
I'll be here.
我一定会来
嘴里有头发
Peh, peh! Hair in my mouth. Peh!
是时候把迷你高尔夫从我的天赋列表里抹掉了
Time to scratch mini golf off my talents list.
不要放弃  梅宝
Aww, don't give up, Mabel.
是啊  如果你这次赢了她
Yeah, if you beat her at this,
她就再也没法嘲笑你了
she could never rag on you again.
想象一下
Imagine it.
丑八怪老太太的服装区在那里
Um, the section for ugly grandma clothes is over there.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
输掉迷你高尔夫的
Well, the section for people
聚集区在那里
who lost at mini golf is over there!
我们已经以最快的速度过来了
We came as fast as we could.
我们听说有个小女孩被严重烧伤了
We heard a little girl got seriously burned!
我完了
I'm ruined!
来击掌
Up top!
你们说得对  伙计们
You're right, guys.
我需要在午夜之前多练习一会儿
I just need to practice a little more before midnight.
你是说  在天黑以后去高尔夫球场
Go to the golf course after dark, you say?
我不知道  难道我们要闯进去
I don't know. We'd have to break in and--
开玩笑的  我们闯进去吧
Just kidding! Let's break in!
还有  梅宝
Oh, and, hey, Mabel!
你最棒
狠狠挫挫她的锐气  孩子
Knock her dead, kid.
见鬼  真见鬼
Darn! Poo-peck-darn!
我不明白
Ugh! I don't get it!
这个洞到底哪不对了
What is wrong with this hole?
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
什么  那是什么声音
What? What is it?
把球杆拿上跟我来
Grab your club.
咱们和平共处  和平共处
We good? We good?
那好吧
All right then.
你们好啊  我叫弗兰兹  欢迎来到我们家
Hi! Hello! I'm Franz. And welcome to our home.
你们是什么生物啊
What is this?
我也想问
Yeah.
你们是小个子的人吗  还是大个子的微型人
Are you guys tiny humans? Or enormous mini-humans?
都不是  我们是迷你高尔夫球僮
Neither. We're lilli-putt-tians!
迷你  迷你高尔夫
Lilli-- Lilli-putt...
这名字还是写出来更好理解
The name makes more sense written out than spoken.
我们的工作就是掌控球的走向  看吧
And we control the balls! Behold!
真是不可思议
That's incredible!
而且复杂得毫无意义啊
And so needlessly complicated.
真是的
Aw, shucks.
这可是我们倾注一生的事业哟
It's only our life-long passion!
想让我们唱首歌来详尽介绍一下吗
Would you like us to elaborate through song?
不用  我们懂了
Nah, we're good.
那么  你们这些大个儿到此有何贵干啊
So what are you hugelings doing here anyway?
我们主要是为了跟我的死对头
We kind of have to play this golf tournament
帕西菲卡来场高尔夫决斗
against my rival, Pacifica.
死对头  死对头  死对头
Oh, rivals. Rivals, rivals.
我们最了解这个了
Oh, we know all about rivals.
穿你的破木屐晃悠吧  风车佬
Put a clog in it, ya windmill lubbers!
你们这群花花公子的技术简直逊爆了
These really bottom popinjays are terrible at controlling the balls!
我们才是真正的控球大师
We are the ball masters, says I!
闭上你的臭嘴  爱炫耀的臭海盗
Shut your mouths, you showboating pirates!
人人都知道埃菲尔铁塔洞才是最棒的
Everyone knows the Eiffel Tower hole is the best!
其实我不懂法语。
最好收回你的话  粗鄙无礼的法国乡巴佬
Stay thee your comments, ye scurrilous Frenchmen!
说到控球技术  没人能比得上来自于
None controllable is better than the knights of...
窝囊废城堡的骑士
Wiener Castle
窝囊废
这谁写的
Who wrote this?
我们将决出谁的球洞是最好的
We'll settle which hole is best!
冲啊
Attack!
给我上
Charge!
哎呦喂  我吓得躲在船里打哆嗦呢
Ooh, I'm shiverin' in me timbers.
准备受死吧
Get ready to die!
迷你国王万岁
Long live the mini king!
去死吧  你这败类
Die, you evil scum!
这些家伙太逗了
These guys are a riot.
各位  各位  淡定  淡定
Guys, guys, calm down.
觉得你们这仗打得莫名喜感
Your fighting is inadvertently adorable.
我们的确很喜感  大个儿  但我们的故事  就不了
Adorable we are, hugeling, but our tale, less so.
这公园里的每一个球洞都认为自己是老大
Every hole in the park thinks that it's superior.
从最东头的牛仔
From the cowboys in the east
到南边肮脏的矿工
to the grimy minors of the south.
要是能有个方法决出谁是最棒的就好了
If only there was some way to decide which side is best
比方说发个奖杯啊什么的
with maybe an award or, like a trophy.
谁知道呢
I don't know.
但是  弗兰兹  快看
But, Franz, look!
你最棒
那个贴纸  那贴纸能决定一切
The sticker. The sticker could decide!
那上面的确写着“最棒”
It does say "the best" on it.
替我们做出选择吧  大个儿
Decide for us, hugeling.
将那贴纸颁给你选中的迷你王国
Choose which mini kingdom to give the sticker to
来结束战争吧
and end our war!
我不知道啊  各位
I don't know, guys.
我不太想掺和到你们这古怪的血海深仇中去
I'm not sure I want to get involved in your weird mini blood feud.
梅宝  这可是个大好机会
Mabel, this is perfect.
球场的球都得听他们的
These guys control the course.
你就告诉他们  你会把贴纸
Just tell them you'll give the sticker
给予对我们获胜帮助最大的那支队伍
to whichever group does a better job of helping us win.
我拿不准啊  迪普
I'm not sure, Dipper.
我确实很想打败帕西菲卡
I want to beat Pacifica,
但这样不就等于作弊吗
but doesn't this seem like cheating?
帕西菲卡是富二代  梅宝  她的整个人生都在作弊
Pacifica's rich, Mabel. She's cheating at life.
谢了兄弟
Thanks, man.
十八个球洞的人民们
People of the 18 holes!
这里将举行一场迷你高尔夫决斗
We're going to have a game of mini-golf!
谁对我获胜的帮助最大
And whoever does the best job helping me win
谁就能获得贴纸
gets the sticker!
你最棒
肯定是我们了  姑娘  而不是这帮郁金香佬
It'll be us, lass, not these tulip munchers.
不许你这种
I will not be insulted
连个耳环都戴跑偏的人侮辱我
by a man with no depth perception wearing earrings.
都给我记住
Just remember,
在你们给我帮忙的时候
as long as you're helping me,
不准互掐
no fighting.
老兄  我要把我衣服领口都剪成W形
Dude, I'm cutting "W"s into all my shirts.
不能和公众的意愿对着干
Got to give the public what they want.
这俩孩子得慢慢来
Well, the kids are taking their time.
估计还要好一会呢
Looks like it's gonna be a while.
今晚肯定有很多星星
Sure are a lot of stars out tonight.
妈呀  这气氛有点不对啊
Well, this is gettin' weird.
给我记住  帕西菲卡  胜利高于一切
Now remember, Pacifica, winning is everything.
哦  哦  还有外表  胜利和外表高于一切
Oh, oh, and also looks. Winning and looks.
老爸  我都练过  差不多  上百万小时的球了
Dad, I've been practicing for, like, a millions hours, okay?
我胜券在握
I've got this.
你们会留下来看我比赛吗
You'll stay to watch, right?
帕西菲卡  亲爱的  我们还有场聚会要去呢
Pacifica, darling. We have a party to go to.
我们看看报纸上你的光辉事迹就行了
We'll just read about your victory in the paper.
谢尔盖
Sergei!
还有  不管发生了什么  永远记住
Oh, and whatever happens, just remember one thing.
你姓诺斯韦斯特
You're a Northwest.
不许输
Don't lose.
你掏多少钱赌他们不敢来
How much do you want to bet they're no shows?
找谁呢
Looking for someone?
躲在暗处啊  一点都不吓人
Waiting in the dark and not creepy at all.
你们居然还真来了啊
Seriously, though?
真不知道你俩为什么来自取其辱
I don't know why you bothered to come.
要么就是你脑子里有事儿睡不着觉
Unless you got something on your sleep.
哦  我们确实有那么一点小本事
Oh, I guess you could say we've got a little something.
是吧  老弟
Right? Right?
十八个球洞  按照标准规则
Eighteen holes. Standard rules.
胜者尽享荣光  输家就永远埋没在耻辱之中
Winner lives in glory. Loser wallows in eternal shame.
各就各位
On your mark,
迷你高尔夫  正式开赛
Get set, Mini golf!
怎么会这样
What?
别挡道
Out of my way!
有没有搞错
Are you serious?
呀哈  必胜
Yarr, I say!
矿工洞
Miner hole.
真想知道  地下都发生了些什么呆萌的事情
I wonder what cute silly things are going on down there.
你们别去啊  里面发生了瓦斯泄漏
You can't go in there! There's been a gas leak.
进去的家伙都得小命玩儿完
Anyone who goes in there will die!
我来吧
I will take it.
不可以
No!
你不能去啊  大亨利  我们需要你
Don't go, Big Henry! We need you!
波莉  回家去
Go home, Polly.
加油啊  大亨利  你能做到的
Come on, Big Henry. You can do this.
啊  不
Aah! No!
谢尔盖  我要喝汽水  现在就要
Sergei! Soda! Now!
好了  各位  刚才简直把她气疯了
Okay, guys, that was badonkulous!
来吧  来击个掌吧  各位
Hey, hey. Little high fives, everyone.
都过来击个掌
Little high fives all around.
干得漂亮  你太棒了  你真牛啊
Nice one. You did it. You're the man!
虽然没打算提前宣布
I don't want to call it out early,
但我说不定会把这个颁给矿工们哦
but I think the Miners might have one of these in their future.
开什么玩笑啊
Are you kidding me?
刚才的活儿都白干了
After everything we've worked for?
冷静点  弗兰兹
Calm yourself, Franz.
还有另外一种方法来赢得大个儿的欢心
There may be another way to win the hugelings' favor.
敲敲木头
Knock on wood.
（注：西方国家认为敲木头可以驱邪  并且带来好运）
这事不太对劲啊  谢尔盖  我能感觉得到
There's something going on, Sergei. I can feel it.
说不定有小小人来控制球的走向呢
Maybe they has little people who control where balls go.
我们该送你去上上英语课
We got to get you English lessons.
我的意思是  仔细想想  我可是在世界上排得上号的选手
I mean, think about it. I'm globally ranked.
前几球她能打败我真是很荒谬
It's ridiculous that she's beating me.
皮特可乐  我总是忘记里面的果核
Ugh, Pitt Cola. I always forget about the pit.
给我换一瓶  谢尔盖
Get me a different one, Sergei.
不好
This is bad.
我都等不及看我们获胜时帕西菲卡的表情了
I can't wait to see the look on Pacifica's face when we win.
我想她的表情会像是这样
I'm thinking it will be like...
你知道她的样子吧
You know how she does that?
迪普  知道她感觉糟糕我就很高兴  我是不是很坏
Dipper, is it bad that I feel good about her feeling bad?
只要享受你的胜利就好  梅宝
Just enjoy your victory, Mabel.
相信我  帕西菲卡会没事的
Trust me, Pacifica will be fine.
发生什么事了  放开我
What's going on here? Let me go!
我错过什么了吗
What did I miss?
放开我  你们这群小怪物
Let me go, you creeps!
欢迎  双胞胎  欢迎
Welcome, twins! Welcome!
我能看出来你们对此很高兴  是吧
I can tell you're loving this, right?
是吧  不是吗
Right? No?
你们都在做什么
What are you guys doing?
协议里可没有这个  小荷兰人
This wasn't part of the deal, tiny Dutchman!
好吧  我们看见你们更喜欢矿工  所以就想
Okay, so we saw you were favoring the Miners and we figured,
比起打败帕菲西卡  什么会更好呢
what's better than beating Pacifica?
就是杀了她  对吗
Killing her, right?
想得美  我要打电话给我爸妈
As if. I'm calling my parents.
我的手机在哪儿
Where is my phone?
你是傻瓜
发送
Send.
发送中
怎么样  现在谁是最棒的  大个儿
So how about it, hugeling? Who's the best now?
话可别说那么早  旱鸭子们
Not so fast, landlubbers!
如果你们要使诈  那我们也会
If you're going to play dirty, so are we.
现在把贴纸给我们  否则他就得走跳板
Now give us the sticker or he walks the plank.
不  把贴纸给我们
No, give us the sticker!
矿工  贴纸是属于矿工的
The Miners! The sticker's for the Miners!
把它给我们  给我们
Give it to us! Give it to us!
别忘了大亨利
Remember Big Henry!
够了
Enough!
知道吗  我谁也不给
You know what? No one gets the sticker!
不  不  不行
No. No. Nuh-uh.
不要发嘘声  停下  停
No booing. Stop. No.
没有人能拿到贴纸  因为你们谁做得都不对
No one gets the sticker 'cause you're all being jerks.
我是说  你们为什么就不能和平相处呢
I mean, why can't you just get along?
因为我们彼此恨对方
Because we hate each other.
这是死对头应该做的  姑娘
That's kinda how rivalries work, lass.
那也许
Well then maybe...
也许当死对头这事傻透了
Maybe rivalries are dumb.
也许你们不该用勾心斗角来解决问题
Maybe you don't settle them with petty competitions.
也许成为"最棒"的唯一方式
Maybe the only way to be "the best"
就是结束对抗共同努力
is by ending the fighting and working together!
看来一切都清楚了
It's all so clear.
如果我们齐心协力
If we work together...
那我们就可以切开她的肚子  拿到贴纸
Then we can cut open her belly and get the sticker.
抓住那个女孩  切了她
Get the girl! Slice her open!
你们这些家伙根本没理解这个道理
You guys aren't appreciating the lesson here!
贴纸  贴纸  贴纸
Sticker! Sticker! Sticker!
救命
Help!
我们必须离开这儿
We've got to get out of here!
我得先救出帕西菲卡
I have to save Pacifica first!
追她
After her!
迪普先生  不要  不要
Ah, Mr. Dipper! <i>Nyet! Nyet!</i>
不要害怕  老兄  这水很浅的
Don't freak out, man! The water's shallow!
绝对淹不死人
There is literally no way to drown.
有没有搞错
Seriously?
哼  你现在才来  小心我的耳环
Ugh, took you long enough. And watch the earrings!
它们可比你家房子值钱
They're worth more than your house!
你知道吗  我改变主意了  也许我不会给你松绑
You know, on second thought, maybe I won't untie you.
给我松绑  松绑
Untie me! Untie me!
这还差不多
That's what I thought.
我们要用微型铅笔头抓住你们
We have you on miniature pencilpoint.
你们被包围了
There's no way around us.
准备好击球了吗
You ready to putt?
早就准备好了
Way ahead of you.
什么
Huh?
你其实没那么糟糕嘛
Hey, you're actually not that terrible.
技术有点生疏  不过
A little rusty, but...
别废话了  专心击球
Just shut up and putt!
快上车  快
Get on! Get on!
快开车
Gun it!
别让他们跑了
Don't let them escape!
谢尔盖掉下来了
Sergei overboard!
我会找个新教练
I'll get a new one.
他们要把我们关在里面
They're shutting us in!
要离开这儿  想都别想
Don't even think about it.
你还称自己是高尔夫球手
You call yourself a golfer?
没有我们  你手里的球杆毫无用处
Without us, that club is useless in your hands.
是么  十减六是多少
Oh yeah? What's ten minus six?
十  等一下
Ten-- Hang on.
死吧
Fore!
待在外面吧  愚蠢的大个儿们
Stay out, you dumb hugelings!
我们之间玩儿完了
We're done with you.
你们说什么  一群小矮人
What did you say, you little trolls?
我要起诉你们
I will sue you.
我要起诉你们  我会成为你们的主人
I will sue you and I will own you.
你们两个
You two.
我不知道你们到底做了什么  发生了什么
I don't know what you did or what's going on,
但如果你们觉得因为救了我的命  我就
but if you think just because you saved my life, I--
对唔起
抱歉  帕西菲卡
I'm sorry, Pacifica.
我们不应该作弊
We shouldn't cheated.
如果公平竞赛  你肯定已经打败我了
You totally would've beat me fair and square.
还好这贴纸我戴着看起来不错  算你们走运
You're just lucky this sticker looks fantastic on me.
嘿  你的父母没来
Hey! You're parents aren't here.
想搭车回家吗
You want a ride home?
拜托  好像我想坐你们的车一样
Puh-leaze, as if I'd ride in your--
开车唱着歌
Singin' the drivin' song
没开车前灯
Headlights are out
看不清目的地
Can't really see where I'm goin'
嘿  我找到了两个墨西哥玉米卷
Hey, I found two tacos!
你们可以在车里吃东西
You're allowed to eat in the car?
是啊  车里会有神秘惊喜的小零嘴
Yeah, the car is where secret surprise snacks happen.
想要吗
Want one?
噢  我不应该要你的施舍
Oh, I'm not supposed to take handouts.
施舍  这叫做分享
Handouts? It's called sharing!
你知道分享是什么吧
You do know what sharing is, right?
分  分享
Shar-- Shaar-ing?
拿着就好
Just take it.
谢谢载我一程  什么的
Thanks for the ride, or whatever.
对了  梅宝
Oh, and Mabel...
不敢相信我会说这种话  但是我今天挺开心
I can't believe I'm saying this but I had fun.
告诉你的仆人  我喜欢他的W领
And tell your servant I like his W neck!
好极了
Yes!
那么你们现在  呃  是和好了吗
So are you guys, like, cool now?
我想我们还是取得了些进展
I think we made some progress.
要记住最重要的是
The important thing to remember is that
归根结底
at the end of the day,
她和我们一样  只是个普通的孩子
she's just an ordinary kid like us.
祝贺帕西菲卡
早知道就应该向她玉米卷的钱
Should've charged her for that taco.
同意
Agreed.
嘿  你们还有惊喜玉米卷吗
Hey, you got any more of those surprise tacos?
你们笑吧  大个儿  弗兰茨会时来运转的
Laugh now, hugelings. But Franz will have his day.
弗兰茨要
Franz will--
陷到沙坑里了
Sand trap! Ow! Ow!
我们操控球  我们操控球
? We control the balls, we control the balls! ?
从伯明翰到蒙特利尔
? From Birmingham to Montreal ?
我们操控球
? We control the balls
伙计们  我想明白了  我们能控制球
Guys I figured it out! We control the balls!
他现在懂了
Now he gets it!
噢  你们这些家伙
Oh, you guys!
我们的生活乐趣永无止境
? Our lives are filled with nonstop fun ?
但是都比不上一杆进洞
? But there's nothing like a hole in one ?
我现在可以走了吗
Can I go now?
永远别想
Never!